<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SwachhaGraha</string>
    <string name="homeUser">Username</string>
    <string name="homePassword">Password</string>
    <string name="homeLogin">Login</string>
    <string name="homeSignUp">SignUp</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="aboutUs">About स्वच्छाग्रह</string>
    <string name="about">Swachhagraha is inspired by one of the largest mass movements - Satyagraha
        that changed the fate of the country. Satyagraha catalysed action, by winning over people\'s
        hearts through tremendous patience and perseverance, instilling in the Indian mind, dignity
        and self respect. It was a freedom movement of the people, by the people and for the people.
        Mahatma Gandhi, who conceptualized Satyagraha, was a staunch believer of the importance of
        sanitation and cleanliness of surroundings in day to day life. He once said, If we do not
        keep our backyards clean our Swaraj will have a foul stench. The project Swachhagraha draws
        inspiration from the Satyagraha movement, to engage people and bring about change similar in
        scale to India\'s freedom movement where people get involved to take action for Creating a
        culture of cleanliness. The project takes inspiration from Swachh Bharat Abhiyan announced
        by the Honourable Prime Minister of India, Shri Narendra Modi. He has emphasized the importance
        of citizen\'s responsibility in sanitation. He says that it is not only the government\'s duty
        but every citizen\'s duty to keep our villages and cities clean.  Swachhagraha is about promoting
        civic consciousness amongst citizens through youth leaders.</string>
</resources>
